A Guide to the Fairfax County History Commission Records, 1967-2019
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 9: Historical Marker Files, 1991-2018
  - Sub-series 9-2: Historical Marker Subject Files, 1992-2015
    - Jack Hiller [clip-on badge], Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Manufacturers, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Marker Committee Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Procedures, 1992-2015 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Replacement Markers, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - SEWAH, 1998-2011 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Standard License Agreement, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Sweig - Old Marker Drafts / Murray - Review of program before 1998, 1992-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - VDHR Replacement Markers, 1999-2011 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - VDOT Marker Installations, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - VDOT Marker Installations, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)